[Music]
[Música]
Lali recorded a video with d review But
ha grabado vídeo Lali con d review Pero
you don't know that, no Ah, I do know, I do
tú no lo sabes eso no Ah yo sí lo sé yo
know, I do know because I
sí lo sé yo sí lo sé porque se lo he
asked her directly, I was going to
preguntado directamente yo se lo iba a
ask her but I say, I don't know, I lost my
preguntar pero digo no sé se me ha ido
mind I was going to ask it
la cabeza Se lo iba a preguntar es que
precisely Hey, I talked to Dallas,
precisamente Oye he hablado con Dallas
but no, no, I lost my mind, I didn't
yo pero no no se me ha ido la cabeza no
remember that at that moment,
me he acordado de eso en ese momento o
so, Dallas, let's see, I'm going to look at
sea que entre Dallas a ver voy voy a
that, it's Yeah, then no Ah, I'm going to
mirar eso son Sí entonces no Ah te voy a
look at the answer she gave me for a moment,
mirar la respuesta que me dio un momento
no, I can't filter it, it depends on how it
no no la puedo filtrar depende de cómo
is for a moment it was a
sea un momento es que era una respuesta
more complex answer than it seems Ah because
más compleja de lo que parece Ah porque
I went crazy and I tell you openly
yo me quedé loco y te digo abiertamente
when I saw that tweet I said, wow, if
yo cuando vi ese tweet dije ostras si
Delas is going to release a video with Lali, I'll
delas va a sacar vídeo con Lali yo me
get one with Rque then I said You know you have to
saco uno con rque entonces dije Sabes
invite me instead of instead of
que me tienes que invitar en vez de en
instead of to the podcast instead of
vez de en vez de al podcast a en vez de
making a podcast you have to invite me to
hacerme un podc me tienes que invitar a
the discussions when you do the discussions
las tertulias cuando hagas las tertulias
this is something that I want to start
esto es una cosa que quiero empezar a
doing at some point I have to  see
hacer en algún momento tengo que ver
how because for now I am your
cómo porque por ahora ahí soy tu
collaborator because most likely he
colaborador porque lo más seguro es que
says but here it is here who is
dice pero aquí está está aquí quién está
up Dallas Dallas is in the chat it will be
sube Dallas Dallas está en el chat será
false Look dasas what a liar XD eh
falso Mira dasas qué mentiroso XD eh
dasas you if you have given me an answer I have not
dasas tú si me has dado respuesta no he
said what answer eh No me don't do me
dicho qué respuesta eh No me no me hagas
13 14 pistachio head is the dasas for
13 14 cabeza pistacho es el dasas de
real yes it was the dasas for real he is in
verdad sí era el dasas de verdad está en
the chat he is in the chat dasas like
el chat está en el chat dasas like
wait dasas Like if you have recorded with
espera dasas Like si has grabado con
Lali dislike if you have not recorded with Lali
Lali dislike si no has grabado con Lali
okay it's that I don't remember when he gave me
vale es que no me acuerdo cuando me dio
the answer from everyone Mod
la respuesta de todos Mod
the answer is neither yes nor no There I'm
la respuesta no es ni sí ni no Ahí os
going to screw you a little since he comes and
voy a [__] un poco ya que venga él y lo
says it if he wants to say it I understand I
diga si quiere decirlo entiendo yo
understand that if Ricky has come to
entiendo que si el Ricky ha llegado a
say that Well of course but the thing is that you ca
decir eso Bueno claro pero es que Ricky
n't trust Ricky because Ricky
no te puedes fiar porque también Ricky
has also said that he has said again eh that
ha dicho que él ha vuelto a decir eh que
he has put a restraining order ad
él ha puesto una orden de alejamiento ad
And you that you think that they buy it at
Y tú eso que te crees que lo compran el
Mercadona damn I mean you let's see that is not
mercadona [__] O sea tú a ver eso no
entirely wrong it is wrong  explained
se equivoca del todo está mal explicado
he went to the police Ricky and told him a
él fue a la policía Ricky y le dijo un
little bit about what was happening to him And they told him if
poco lo que le pasaba Y le dijeron si
tomorrow you want to report Dallas you can't
mañana quieres denunciar a Dallas no
approach him because you can't
puedes acercarte a él porque no puedes
report that someone is threatening you
denunciar que alguien te está amenazando
with whatever if later you are recording
de lo que sea si luego tú estás grabando
a podcast with him or you are meeting
un podcast con él o estás quedando en
him in person or you are confronting
persona con él o te estás confrontando a
him you know what they say I don't remember
él sabes elas dice no recuerdo haber
saying anything What the [ __ ] he made it up
dicho nada What the fuck se lo ha
Ricky made it up
inventado se lo ha inventado el Ricky
completely I'll release videos about
por completo pronto saco vídeos sobre
it soon I mean no and I'm too excited I
eso o sea que no y yo too ilusionado yo
watched a newscast today but let's see let's
me he sacado hoy un noticiero pero a ver
see It's that I had one the dasas
a ver Es que a mí me dio una el dasas
maybe you deleted my
puede ser que me hayas borrado el
message from the discord [ __ ] to m to me it
mensaje del discord cabrón a m a mí me
made sense I thought what I said Today it made sense to me more than
cuadraba yo lo que he dicho Hoy era me
look in
cuadra má que mira
box but apart from the fact that Dallas
encado pero aparte que el Dallas
recording in person I didn't see it okay
grabando en persona no lo veía yo vale
look here here here I can get the
mira aquí aquí me aquí me pued el
message tip I can read what you
mensaje tip puedo leer lo que me
answered me I can answer what you
respondiste puedo responder lo que me
told me on discord I'll send it to you
dijiste por discord te lo mando por
privately the answer I'll give you an
privado la respuesta te hago un resumen
easy summary if I'm omitting things taking it
fácil si omitiendo cosas tomando por
privately if he's telling you  that doesn't say
privado si te está diciendo que no dice
no that he's a liar whoever
que no que es un mentiroso el tipo que
is telling you no yes no He
sea que te está diciendo que no sí no Él
told me he told me that he wasn't going to release a
me dijo él me dijo que no iba a sacar
video no no no no that no that you haven't deleted
vídeo no no no que no que no has borrado
anything it was me that couldn't find it I
nada era yo que no lo encontraba he
liked the search engine and I already
gustado el buscador y ya lo he
found it I sent it privately
encontrado lo he mandado por privado
This is what you answered me if you
Esto es lo que me respondiste tú si
want to upload
quieres subir
eh If you want to upload be here until 4
eh Si quieres subir est aquí hasta las 4
in the morning again debating eh come on
de la mañana otra vez debatiendo eh dala
If you want to upload I'll send you the link ci
Si quieres subir te mando el link cí
tell me on discord first it says upload yes to you
amelo en discord primero dice sube sí te
Ah I put it in a private
lo Ah te lo he puesto por privado de
discord Eh well I can quote it to you
discord Eh bueno te lo puedo citar
too eh Okay but if what he's
también eh Bueno pero si lo si lo está
denying it is that no what I don't know is that
desmintiendo es que no lo que no sé es
Ricky then hears the bell and
que el Ricky entonces escucha campana y
comes to his conclusion and that's it No a Eh
se saca su conclusión y punto No a Eh
well no yes He shot a three-pointer That's the
bueno no sí Se tiró un triple Ese es el
summary Ah phew okay now
resumen Ah puf vale ahora lo está
Dallas is reading it let's see what he says but
leyendo Dallas a ver qué dice pero
listen to me I mean the guy hits a three-pointer
escúchame o sea el tío se pega un triple
for what I think Ah
para qué yo creo Ah
better Okay seems good to me Okay then The
mejor Okay me parece bien Okay pues La
answer is no that he hasn't recorded a
respuesta es que no que no ha grabado
video That's the answer that  I can give
vídeo Esa es la respuesta que puedo dar
according to my source Dallas allows me
según mi fuente Dallas me permite
now no, it sounded to me that I don't know if
ahora no yo me sonaba que no sé si el
Dallas in some in some video tells her
Dallas en alguna en algún vídeo le dice
if you want to come come and talk I don't
de si quieres venirte vente a hablar no
know what no how much we are going to approach it in
sé qué no cuánto lo vamos a plantear de
another way but in a way an
otra manera pero de una manera de una
easy way he hasn't recorded anything he hasn't said that he is
manera fácil no ha grabado nada no ha
not going to record it he said
dicho que no vaya a grabarlo ha dicho
that he hasn't recorded it I mean he hasn't
que no lo ha grabado O sea a mí no me ha
told me and if not let him say it through the chat He has
dicho y si no que lo diga él por el chat
n't told me no never I am
A mí no me ha dicho no nunca Tengo
thinking of recording with her what he
pensado grabar con ella a mí lo que me
told me is that I have not recorded anything And that is
ha dicho es no he grabado nada Y eso es
a reality the way he is
una realidad de la forma que lo está
saying it in the chat it smells to me like
diciendo en el chat me huele a que no
there is no plan I don't know Possibly no the
hay ni plan no sé Posiblemente no la
question is what would I gain by recording with
pregunta es qué ganaría grabando con
her no also It should be a question
ella no también Debería ser una pregunta
in the end I think that in this case in the
al final yo creo que en este caso en la
story it is the one who has done
historia esta la al es quien lo ha hecho
wrong, I mean Ricky has made his mistakes
mal o sea Ricky ha cometido sus fallos
But mainly the one who has done
Pero principalmente quien lo ha hecho
wrong is Lali I mean she is also the reason why they
mal es Lali o sea también es el motivo
ask me why you haven't
por el que me preguntan por qué no has
brought or rather the two of them in the first
traído o sea los dos yo en la primera
part of let's see I think I think let's see I
parte de a ver yo creo yo creo a ver yo
think she has done it  Lali is much worse than
creo que lo ha hecho mucho peor Lali que
Ricky, much worse, man, of course, let's see,
Ricky muchísimo peor hombre claro a ver
man, pretending is pretending that they've
es que hombre fingir sea fingir que te
done a V to you, pretending that I've done one, surpassed
han hecho una V fingir que hecho una
all the liars that we
superado a todas las mentirosas que
had talked about H at this moment she has
habíamos comentado H este momento ha
surpassed them all, eh, she has surpassed, I do
superado a todas eh es que ha superado
n't know if even what I'm telling you, but but but
no sé si hasta lo que te digo pero pero
Ricky the sailor girl Ricky, I mean, Ricky
pero Ricky la marinerita Ricky o sea
took it first, that's something I
Ricky cogió primero eso es una cosa que
had to comment on today, that Ricky
tenía para comentar hoy que que Ricky
takes it and says, he didn't involve me, he used my
coge y dice no me involucró usó mi
speakerphone and it's like, no, no, he didn't use your
altavoz y es como no no no usó tu
speakerphone, you ignored her, you ignored
altavoz tú pasaste de ella tú pasaste de
her completely, eh When you
ella completamente eh Cuando te
found out about the situation, you made her put up a
enteraste del percal la hiciste poner un
thread, then you were going to break up with her, but
hilo luego ibas a cortar con ella pero
when you saw that everything, I mean, what about Ricky
cuando viste que todo o sea lo de Ricky
was a move, Ricky made a teaser
fue una movida Ricky la hizo un teaser
for, I mean, he made a teaser to make
para o sea hizo un teaser para hacerle
a series for her, and then he recorded the series
una serie ardala y luego la serie la
twice because he recorded it with
grabó dos veces porque una la grabó con
her once and since they criticized him, he recorded it later
ella y como le criticaron la grabó luego
alone again, let's see, I understand. Look, I, I have,
solo otra vez a ver yo entiendo Mira yo
I have appreciation for
yo es que le tengo yo le tengo aprecio a
Ricky. So for my part, I see it
Ricky Entonces por por mi parte lo veo
maybe in a different way because
quizá de una manera distinta porque
Also when that happened he stayed
también cuando pasó eso él él quedó
with me and explained to me what happened later,
conmigo y me explicó lo que luego o sea
that is, when he made the video, being
cuando él ya hizo el vídeo ese
honest, I already knew that some time
sincerando yo eso ya lo sabía tiempo
before and he didn't change his version, the version he
antes y no cambió la versión la versión
tells in that video is the same one he
que cuenta en ese vídeo es la misma que
told to his close circle. So
contó a su círculo cercano Entonces yo
what I can tell you is that there were
lo que te puedo decir es que él hubo
videos in which he told one thing,
vídeos en los que contaba una cosa
knowing another because he was afraid that
Sabiendo otra porque tenía miedo a que
that person, because that person was
esa persona porque esa persona le estaba
threatening him that he was going to take his
amenazando en que se iba a quitar la
life, yes, yes, he said according to what
vida si si él si él decía según Qué
things. So I understand that it is a
cosas Entonces yo entiendo que es una
very delicate situation, I told
situación muy delicada yo se lo dije a
him it is a very delicate situation, I also
él es una situación muy delicada también
recommended that he not lie, that he be
le recomendé que no mintiera que fuera
honest, and that if the other person wants to do whatever it
honesto y que si la otra quiere hacer lo
is, it is her responsibility but not
que sea es su responsabilidad pero no la
his because, let's see, let's see, let's see,
suya porque a ver a ver a ver a ver
wait. So Ricky catches his girlfriend,
espera O sea que Ricky Pilla a la novia
uh, on the phone, he catches conversations
eh por teléfono le pilla conversaciones
where she wants to continue [ __ ] the guy
donde quiere seguir follándose al tío
she [ __ ] while she was with him and that she
que se folló estando con él y y que se
wants to go partying with him again and
quiere volver a ir de fiesta con él y
that she is trying to meet up with him
que está intentando quedar con él
secretly while she acts in front of Ricky
escondida mientras hace delante de Ricky
as if it were normal and that he takes her
como si fuera normal y que él coge se la
to Andorra, records  a teaser and not
lleva a andorra graba un teaser y no
all of that is later the the that part
todo eso es posterior el el el esa parte
of the information no but wait are you
de información no pero espérate me estás
telling me that he takes her to Andorra
diciendo que él coge se la lleva andorra
records a teaser records a series against
graba un teaser graba una serie contra
Dala records another series against Dala and and he
dala graba otra serie contra dala y y él
calls the guy his
llama violador al chico con el que se
girlfriend is sleeping with a rapist and his
acuesta la novia y maltratador al es
boyfriend an abuser knowing that it is a lie for fear that he might
novio sabiendo que es mentira por miedo
attempt suicide Look
a que tenga un intento autolítico Mira
here the point is first of all and in
aquí el el punto es en primer lugar y en
the first information that you share with me
la primera información que me compartes
or that she wants to repeat and all that
o de que ella quiere repetir y todo eso
secretly I think she finds out
a escondidas eso creo que le descubre
later because she never told me that I
más tarde porque eso a mí no me lo contó
saw that later when it
nunca yo eso lo vi luego cuando cuando
came out in the video and all that So no no no no
salió en el vídeo y todo eso Entonces no
no saying no it's what he's
no diciendo no es que eso es lo que está
saying it's the time no when
diciendo es la hora no cuando ya me
the information already reached me he reads the
llegó la información él leen los
messages and he says it in the video with her he
mensajes y lo dice en el vídeo con ella
says it he says that he's seeing how
lo dice é él dice que está viendo como
the girlfriend is trying to organize another
la novia está intentando organizar otra
party with the guys I if you want I
fiesta con los chavales yo si quieres yo
if you want since time has passed I
si quieres como ya ha pasado tiempo te
can tell you what he told me Of course to
puedo contar lo que a mí me dijo Claro a
me what he told me that day we were
mí lo que me dijo que ese día estábamos
Agustn we were  he was there was me and
Agustín estábamos él est estaba yo y
some other friend he told me look
algún amigo más él me dijo Mira ha
this happened I'm feeling bad about this eh this
pasado esto estoy mal por esto eh esta
person has probably been unfaithful to me
persona me ha seguramente sido infiel
okay eh that's the theory that he had I didn't
vale eh es la teoría que él tenía no
have the certain confirmation But I had
tenía la confirmación certera Pero tenía
a strong suspicion I'm afraid that's how it was I
una gran sospecha me Temo que ha sido
think he's hiding it this
así Creo que está ocultándolo de esta
way and he's telling me that if I'm
manera y me está diciendo que como yo
going to say something or do
vaya a decir algo o yo vaya a hacer
anything he'll take his life so
cualquier cosa se quita la vida entonces
I told him [ __ ] what a [ __ ] madness I mean
yo le dije hostias Qué [__] locura O sea
I was shocked that's why I came
yo me quedé de piedra por eso yo venía
here trying to calm the waters
aquí intentaba apaciguar las las aguas
because it
porque
's a crazy situation I think it's really really difficult
es una situ muada creo es mu mu difícil
then from there he started to
entonces a partir de ahí lo empezó a
manage it badly he himself saw how his
gestionar fatal él mismo vio como su
career was going down the drain and look he
carrera se estaba yendo a pique y mira
was in his Prime The truth is that I
que estaba en su Prime La verdad que me
felt really bad because he's a guy that I
supo muy mal porque es un tío que a mí
like the content that he makes that
me Mola el contenido que hace que de
again I know that there are differences and that he
nuevo sé que hay diferencias y que no
isn't good with certain people and that
sea bien con ciertas personas y que a
sometimes he puts in let's say he puts his foot in it with
veces mete mete digamos mete la pata con
some topics but there I do think he
algunos temas pero ahí sí creo que lo
did very badly and well yay dude I'm
hizo muy mal y bueno yalas tío te lo
telling you seriously the worst of all is that
digo en serio es que lo peor de todo es
I know that  they're going to kill but if they
que yo sé que se llevan a matar pero si
had met under other
se hubieran conocido en otras
circumstances it would vary a lot because
circunstancias se varía muy bien porque
I know them both and they have a
yo los conozco a los dos y tienen un
very similar Flow man that's what I said that's what
Flow muy parecido tío eso decía eso
I said before this happened and
decía yo antes de que pasara esto y
with me Ricky behaved really dirty I mean
conmigo Ricky se portó guarr simo o sea
because I behaved too well with him
porque demasiado bien me porté con él
for like him Dallas comes up you're
para como él Dallas sube lo estás
wanting it Dallas is like a Maruja in
deseando Dallas está como una Maruja en
the corner saying he's going to put on the
la esquinita diciendo se va a poner el
Avatar that his eyes close
Avatar que que se le cieran los ojos
saying I'll be back in 5 minutes and I'm going to
diciendo vengo 5 minutos y me voy a
sleep and he's going to stay TR hours eh yeah
dormir y se va a quedar TR horas eh si
sure his house Damn What nonsense
claro su casa [__] Que tontería deo
total with er here be let's see I
total con er aquí sea vamos a ver yoo
said that because I me I had a
decía eso porque yo me yo tuve una
cordial relationship with Ricky but like Look it's
cordialidad con Ricky pero en plan A ver
not like we were friends but he
no es que fuéramos amigos pero él
we met Well I think the
nosotros nos conocimos Bueno creo que la
first time we talked was because he
primera vez que hablamos fue porque él
attacked me he grabbed he spread those
me atacó él cogió le dio difusión a las
conversations that he published about me
conversaciones esas que publicó de mi
Win michu calling me a dirty old man
Win michu llamándome viejo verde
calling me a lot of things while
llamándome un montón de cosas mientras
he defended eh eh For example to
que él defendía eh eh Por ejemplo a
chocas that at 30 years old if he wanted to be
chocas que con 30 años si quería estar
with an 18 year old No  I know things like that okay he
con una de 18 No sé cosas así vale me
called me old Green he attacked me a lot of
llamó viejo Verde me atacó un montón de
things to defend Win Macho And
cosas para defender al Win Macho Y
after that Of course in the debate I
después de eso Claro en el debate yo
entered calmly I put him in his place I don't
entré calmadito le puse en su sitio no
know what and we got along cordially
sé qué y nos llevamos bien cordialmente
he mentioned me in his live streams and in
él me mencionaba en sus directos y en
his videos in a good way I also
sus vídeos para bien yo a él también
reacted to his things in fact he
reaccionamos sus cosas de hecho me
sent me things for me to react too and so on and so on and we have
mandaba cosas para yo reaccionar también
even been
y demás no y hemos estado incluso
talking we have had calls I do
hablando nos hemos hemos tenido llamadas
n't remember what topic but anyway
no me acuerdo de qué tema pero bueno
calls that we have both been
llamadas que hemos estado los dos
Chatting here until the early hours on
Charlando aquí hasta las tantas en
discord okay for per call but
discord vale por por llamada pero de
suddenly He doesn't understand why I have to
repente Él no entiende que yo tenga que
comment on his girlfriend's issue but also
comentar su tema de su novia pero aparte
looking for the truth And if I have some
buscando la verdad Y si yo tengo una
information that your girlfriend has cheated on you
información que es tu novia te ha puesto
dude open your eyes and
los cuernos colega abre los ojos y
besides in the first videos what
aparte yo en los primeros vídeos lo que
I was saying was I don't believe at all that that was
yo decía era yo no me creo para nada que
a rape there is this
eso haya sido una violación hay este
clue this clue this clue she
indicio este indicio este indicio te
is cheating on you dude open your eyes and I was saying it's
está engañando tío abre los ojos y yo
not his fault it's
decía él no tiene la culpa la culpa la
her fault now where I start to
tiene ella ahora donde yo ya empiezo a
give him marismea wood is when he
darle leña marismeña es cuando él le
is following the lead of the chick that I  I
está siguiendo el rollo a la pava que yo
think he does it for ego so
creo que lo hace por ego para no
he doesn't feel like the internet conudo and
sentirse él como el conudo de internet y
when he continues with the spiel that
cuando Él sigue con la matraca de que
tudor is an abuser it's like uncle But
tudor es un maltratador es como tío Pero
if I have tudor here if the
si yo tengo aquí a tudor si es que la
complaint is this man let's see when I saw I
denuncia es esto tío a ver yo cuando vi
recognize when I saw the chat with
yo reconozco cuando vi la La charla con
tudor not the one you say the ex like me
tudor no el que dices tú el ex como yo
there I also had information I said
ahí ya también tenía información dije
poor kid I felt so sorry for the guy I
pobre chaval me dio mucha lástima el tío
thought he was a [ __ ] great guy and for
me parecía un tío de [__] madre y para
the people I tell you the people who say
la gente te lo digo la gente que dice
delox it looks good I think I've already
delox bien queda creo que ya he
shown that I am anything but good it
demostrado que soy de todo menos bien
looks Because if I come here for free and I
queda Porque si vengo aquí de gratis y
give four snot to people who I think
meto cuatro mocos a gente que creo que
deserve it what happens is that again I
se lo merece lo que pasa que de nuevo Yo
understand that Dallas can have his
entiendo que Dallas puede tener sus
differences with Ricky If I were Dallas
diferencias con Ricky Si yo fuera Dallas
and Ricky would have told me what Ricky
y Ricky me hubiera dicho lo que Ricky le
has said to Dallas and vice versa no If I
ha dicho a Dallas y viceversa no Si yo
were Ricky Dallas would have told him what he
fuera Ricky Dallas le hubiera dicho lo
said to Ricky I understand that they do not
que le ha dicho a Ricky Yo entiendo que
get along or rather perfect it has made him a
se lleven mal o sea perfect le ha hecho
man obviously I understand that well that they
hombre obviamente entiendo que pues que
dedicate videos to him in a
le dediquen vídeos en un momento
delicate moment he has done it to him  taken as an
delicado él se lo ha tomado como un
attack again you are a figure the balls
ataque de nuevo eres figura los huevos
the other has done it seven series with
lo ha hecho el otro siete series con la
Lita man cl but But Javi Javi do you
Lita hombre cl pero Pero Javi Javi
understand that this is the myth that
entiendes que esto es la mítica de que
one tells him the other tells him that
uno le dice el otro le dice que que de
again I totally agree that
nuevo yo Estoy totalmente de acuerdo en
one has the right to make their videos
que uno tiene derecho a hacer sus vídeos
if they want and the other to respond the same, I mean I
si quiere y el otro igual de responder o
think that here in the end
sea yo creo que aquí al final todo el
everyone has their right of expression
mundo tiene su derecho de de expresión
of anyway that's it let's
de de todos modos es
see I really swear to you that I
eso a ver yo de verdad te lo juro que yo
have nothing against Ricki apart from the fact that he
no tengo nada en contra ricki aparte de
is a big liar okay but eh Let's see
que es muy mentiroso vale pero eh A ver
but but he told me this and that and that So I
pero pero me ha dicho esto y lo otro y
have that against him
lo otro Entonces eso lo tengo en contra
you'll forgive me but the guy does I do
me vas a perdonar pero el colega le hace
n't know if he had 20 or 30 videos
no sé si llevaba 20 o 30 vídeos en
against Dallas on his main channel
contra de Dallas en su canal principal
okay on his main channel okay I
vale en su canal principal vale Yo no
'm not against them making 30 videos
estoy en contra de que hagan 30 vídeos
about anyone because I make 100 about other people
de nadie porque yo hago 100 de la gente
okay But what you can't do is
vale Pero lo que tú no puedes hacer es
that when he does one to you I'm going to
que cuando te hace a ti él uno me voy a
put a restraining order on him As if
poner una orden de alejamiento Como si
you request that at the city hall or
eso lo solicitas tú en el ayuntamiento o
something like that  like Sorry friend
algo por el estilo como Perdona amigo
that Dallas has made a video you
que el Dallas ha hecho un vídeo tú lo
did it on the 30th I mean jaw How do you
has hecho el 30 o sea mandíbula Cómo se
say that glass jaw but
dice eso mandíbula de cristal pero puño
iron fist No I'm telling you eh I
de hierro No yo estoy te digo eh yo
I totally agree that in this
Estoy totalmente de acuerdo que en este
case dasas has an obviously
caso dasas tiene una posición obviamente
more solid position than the one he could have
pues más sólida que la que pueda tener
that he did wrong but again I know him
él que él lo ha hecho mal pero de nuevo
in person and I think
Es que yo lo conozco en persona y creo
that many people if they knew each other behind the
que mucha gente si se conociera detrás
scenes would change their opinions
de pantallas cambiaría la opinión de
that he acted wrong does not
otras personas que él haya actuado mal
imply that he is a bad person I don't
no implica que sea mala persona yo no
think Ricky is a bad person that's
creo que Ricky sea mala persona eso es
where I'm getting to he did
donde yo quiero llegar que lo ha hecho
wrong bad person has reasons to
mal mala persona tenga motivos para
put him in his place he will know or whatever I
ponerlo en su sitio él sabrá o sea
totally agree if he considers
Totalmente de acuerdo si él considera
that there are reasons I think that daras is a
que hay motivos Yo creo que daras es un
very sane guy I mean he's a guy that I
tío muy cuerdo o sea es un tío que yo le
respect a lot because he really shows
respeto mucho porque realmente demuestra
judgment So if he wants to make a
criterio Entonces si él quiere tirar un
video let him make one two three or five I
vídeo que le tire uno dos tres o cinco o
mean I'm not going to tell him not to do
sea yo no le voy a decir que no haga
anything it's his [ __ ] job too you know
nada es su [__] trabajo también sabes
but but it makes me laugh because
pero pero me hace gracia porque
obviously thas I think he's
obviamente thas yo creo que se está
biting his tongue there and there's the guy who
mordiendo ahí la lengua y está el tío
no longer  I
no ya me
see dasas Dalas [ __ ] who's
veo dasas Dalas cabrón que me está
listening to me then don't encourage me here
escuchando luego no me hagas aquí un
and tell me with condemnations to Ricky don't
nimo y me digas con condenas a Ricky no
[ __ ] with me eh No Look, it's not that he's, see
me jodas eh No A ver no es que sea a ver
for me a bad person would be well
para mí una mala persona serían pues
some of those that I have brought to the
algunos de los que yo he traído a a los
gameover no and and pocu or someone like that no to
gameover no y y pocu o alguien así no a
see one thing a bad person but him It's that
ver una cosa una mala persona pero el Es
I Sorry that Sorry to cut you off
que yo Perdón que Perdón que te corte
Javi is that you have some moderators that I
Javi es que tienes unos moderadores que
gave them a hug they say no insist
les daba un abrazo dicen no insist
you are Dalas does not upload without 15 likes and they
estáis Dalas no sube sin 15 likes y ya
have already learned from the best eh Already asking for
han aprendido del mejor eh Ya pidiendo
likes the moderators Ah sure sure
likes los moderadores Ah claro claro
listen to me but what is it that it does not have It does not
escúchame pero que que es que no tiene
have because I have gotten along well with
No tiene por yo me he llevado bien con
him getting along with Dallas I mean, it
con él llevándome con Dallas o sea yo no
has nothing to do with me getting along with one
tiene nada que ver que me lleve con uno
I get along with a lot of people with whom
yo me llevo con mucha gente con las que
Dallas does not get along it has nothing to
el Dallas se lleva mal no tiene nada que
do we are adults okay but Honestly
ver somos adultos vale pero Honestamente
Ricky I expected something else from him I mean yes it
el Ricky yo me esperaba otra cosa de él
's true that the day he
o sea sí que es verdad que a mí el día
pissed me off the day he did
me tocó los huevos el día que me hizo
that to me but I  I have one thing that for
eso a mí pero yo tengo una cosa que para
better or worse I'm an idiot And it's that
bien o para mal soy [__] Y es que
I don't hold a grudge in the end we ended up
yo no tengo rencor al final acabamos
well it was content, come on, okay, but
bien era contenido venga fuera vale pero
there's the way of carrying it I said it's not
ahí ya la manera de llevarlo yo dije no
normal for a person who goes in the
es normal en una persona que va en los
videos as if condemning the feminist
vídeos como condenando a la feminista
criticizing I don't know who watching
criticando a no sé quién viendo los
Roma Gallardo's videos No it's not normal
vídeos de Roma Gallardo No no es normal
that now he follows Win michu's thing
que ahora le siga el rollo al Win michu
but I say Well it will be because of the friendships he
pero digo Bueno será por las amistades
has and and I and I thought the
que tiene y y yo y yo me pensaba eso
same thing and the dala can tell you the same thing
mismo y el dala te puede decir lo mismo
that you have told me I have told him
que tú me has dicho a mí se lo he dicho
many times, surely if you
yo a él muchas veces seguro que si os
had met in another context
hubierais conocido en otro contexto
because you have many things I have
porque tenéis muchas cosas eso se lo he
told him that but seeing what
dicho a él pero viendo lo que ha hecho
this guy has done here, what I get the
aquí este tío a mí lo que me da la
impression is that he plays a role he tries to
impresión que hace un papel se intenta
give the role of a sadist of Roma Gallardo
dar un papel de sadete de Roma Gallardo
in his live shows but then he is not, I
en sus directos pero luego no lo es o
mean then his girlfriend catches him
sea luego coge la parienta la pilla
cheating on him and what he does is
poniéndole los cuernos y lo que hace es
first what he did was he doesn't want to
primero lo que hizo fue no lo quiere
put it because it's a thing of his
poner porque es una cosa de su vida
private life But he wants his
privada Pero quiere que de alguna manera
girlfriend to pay for it somehow  it's like you have to
la novia lo pague es como tú tienes que
pay for what you've done to me and he makes her
pagar lo que me has hecho y la hace
post a thread then when she posts the thread
poner un hilo luego cuando pone el hilo
they shoot the relative they want to
acribillan a la parienta lo quieren
take him for rape for the drugs I don't know that I do
llevar por la violación por la droga no
n't know how much but of course that's the
sé que no sé cuánto pero claro eso es el
issue of rape and he himself doesn't
tema de la violación é él mismo no se lo
believe it a guy who follows the content that he
cree un tío que sigue el contenido que é
follows and who talks about the things that he
sigue y que habla de las cosas que él
talks about his relative comes to him after
habla le llega la parienta después de
having taken the messages that he has
haber cogido los mensajes que le ha
taken and tells him that it was a
cogido y le dice que eso ha sido una
rape and says you're raping
violación y dice tú me estás violando a
me your mind okay you're catching on To
mí la mente vale tú te estás cachando A
me what happens is that he goes along with the
mí lo que pasa es que él le sigue el
rape thing so as not to
rollo de lo de la violación para no
feel like a cuckold to not feel
sentirse un cornudo para no sentirse
humiliated here about the whole story the
humillado aquí de toda la historia de
whole story that you told I didn't
toda la historia que has contado no lo
know that he didn't know one fact I'm not going
sabía que no se sabía un dato no lo voy
to give it I'm not going to give it because no I don't
a dar no lo voy a dar porque no no
want to confuse things more than they already
quiero liar la troca más de lo que ya
are but there is a fundamental fact of the
está pero hay un dato fundamental de la
story that is not like that Or at least it is not
historia que no es así O al menos no es
the official version that was told to us
la versión oficial que se nos contó
then There may be a little
entonces Puede que haya una
lie
mentirijillas
story ri in the video that he makes with
historia ri en el vídeo que hace con
her  Ricky claims that he caught her on the
ella Ricky afirma que la ha cogido en el
phone but apart from that it's
teléfono pero es que aparte es es de es
from ABC let's see they catch her on the
de ABC vamos a ver le cogen en el
phone no longer conversations with the
teléfono ya no conversaciones con los
notes in which she wants to meet up with them
notas en las que quiere quedar con ellos
and have another party with the guy who
y hacer otra fiesta con el tío que te ha
raped you okay but there are
violado vale sino que hay mensajes
deleted messages with her friends where they talk about
borrados con las amigas donde hablan de
cheating on Ricky Well I don't know if they talk
engañarle a Ricky Bueno no sé si hablan
about cheating on Ricky in which she catches him
de engañarle a Ricky en los que le pilla
anyways Turn up the mic now I
de todos modos de Súbele el micro ahora
have it under e Let's see dasas [ __ ] eh
lo tengo yo bajo e A ver dasas cabrón eh
over there that V full throttle first I'll
para allá que V a tope lo primero le
buy him I'll buy him what dasas says there's
compro le compro lo que dice dasas hay
a Son son fex no who says that I
un Son son fex no que dice que que lo
see him with better eyes because I like him it's
veo con mejores ojos porque me cae bien
clear when you like someone you
está claro cuando alguien te cae bien lo
see him with better eyes or you are more
ves con mejores ojos o eres más
permissive Eh yes I admit it I'm passing
permisivo Eh sí lo reconozco estoy pasa
clear but I'm never going to be a
clar pero que yo no voy a hacer nunca al
hypocrite I'm going to tell you the truth I
hipócrita yo os voy a decir la verdad yo
'm biased he's a guy who
estoy sesgado es un tío que a mí nunca
has never treated me badly and I don't think he has done
me ha tratado mal y creo que no ha hecho
anything serious enough for
nada lo suficientemente grave como para
me to cross him if he got a kiss
que yo lo cruce si se hiciera un coscu
obviously  would cross do I explain or not I
obviamente lo cruzaría me explico o no
mean for me there are some lines yes yes
Es decir para mí hay unas líneas si si
a friendship of mine An acquaintance of mine crosses
una amistad mía Un conocido mío supera
a line [ __ ] and and Dalas too so you don't
una línea hostias y y Dalas también para
get jealous Ricky is an
que no te pongas celoso Ricky es
acquaintance of mine I like you better we're more
conocido mío tú me caes mejor somos más
friends with you dasas don't worry
amigos contigo dasas no te preocupes
okay You can take that you take
vale Ya te puedes llevar esa te llevas
that much don't worry with Ricky
ese tanto no te preocupes con con Ricky
I have the relationship of having
yo tengo pues la relación de haber
met him four or five times and that's it The thing is
quedado cuatro o cinco veces con él y ya
that I get along well
está Lo que pasa que me llevo bien
because I treat people well you know it
porque pues trato bien a la gente sabes
or not and I think it's going to end up going up
o no e y creo que va terminar subiendo
eh Leave 15 likes friends and the other one is that
eh Dejad 15 likes amigos e y la otra es
I think the story man is so
eso yo creo que la historia tío está tan
badly told the first video It's insane
mal contada el primer vídeo Es demencial
bad okay the one where they sit down and
malo vale el el de que se sientan y
put on a whole show what is writing
hacen todo el show qué está escribiendo
privately to Dallas to convince him
por privado a Dallas para convencerle
that he sees you very focused No it's not my
que te ve muy concentrado No no es a mi
wife my wife I was going to tell you that
mujer a mi mujer esto te iba a decir que
today I asked myself I today today I
hoy me lo preguntaba Yo hoy hoy me lo
asked myself and you what time do you get
preguntaba yo e tú a qué hora te
up 1 o'clock it depends on the time
levantas la 1 las do depende la hora que
I feel at night
me dé por la noche
and And you have and you have  you
y Y tú tienes y tú tienes
act like a father is that I said this poor
haces de padre es que yo dije el pobre
guy I don't know where he gets time for the
tío este no s dónde saca tiempo para la
family for work you're on all
familia para el trabajo estás en todos
the [ __ ] channels come out man see how
los [__] canales sale hombre a ver la
lucky you are to work here at
suerte que tienes de trabajar aquí en
home it's that you want it or not well when you
casa es que quieras que no pues cuando
're not live you record a video
no estás en directo tú grabas un vídeo
you're here but you're here come in go
estás aquí pero estás aquí entra s va
to the living room eat a snack go downstairs for a
para el salón come merienda bajas un
while take a walk today we went for
rato a da una vuelta hoy hemos ido por
example to Huelva where we go a lot on the
ejemplo a a huelva que vamos mucho fin
weekends but oh well let's see what's
de semana pero bueno a ver qué es lo que
there This isn't easy if you want to get
hay Esto no es fácil si quieres sacar
something out no no I can't imagine I can imagine and
algo no no me imagino me imagino y
getting back to the subject so they don't tell me
retomando el tema para que no me digan
that I'm changing the subject places that I don't change the
que cambio de tema lugares que no cambio
subject [ __ ] genuine question that
de tema [__] pregunta genuina que me ha
came to mind eh what dasas says I did
venido a la cabeza eh lo que dice dasas
n't say that you have to cross him what I'm
no he dicho que lo tengas que cruzar lo
saying is don't try to put On the
que digo es que no intentes poner Al
same level that he may be angry
mismo nivel que él puede estar enfadado
with me because we're not On the same level
conmigo porque no estamos Al mismo nivel
for example because of what we've already talked about yes I'll buy you that Take I'll
por ejemplo por lo ya hablado sí te
buy you that Take yes
compro ese Take te compro ese Take sí
yes it's true that in this dasas he's
que sí que es cierto que en esta dasas
right but what is that
tiene tiene razón pero qué es eso que
maybe guys Lali issue you [ __ ] that you put me on
igual chicos tema Lali cabrones que me
I'm always in trouble that's the bad thing about getting into trouble because at the end of the day you have to understand that I'm honest with you, man, I mean, I wish I could tell you something else so you'd be happier but I don't care if on this channel you
da igual que en este canal os caiga
genuinely dislike Ricky or if there's a large
genuinamente mal Ricky o haya un gran
percentage of people who dislike
porcentaje de gente que le caiga mal
Ricky because he's behaved well with me
Ricky porque conmigo se ha portado bien
So until he does something very
Entonces hasta que no haga algo muy
serious I can't say cross him in
grave yo no lo puedo digamos cruzar de
any way maybe my words have not
ningún modo quizá mis palabras no han
been the best well I'm sorry It
sido las mejores pues lo siento Lo que
's 2 in the morning I'm half
son las 2 de la mañana vengo medio medio
asleep no but of course you see it
dormido no pero claro es que tú lo ves
as a conflict between the two of us
como un conflicto entre entre los dos
but it's objectively clear to me
pero es que objetivamente claro para mí
Look you know how I see it, I genuinely
Mira sabes cómo lo veo yo genuinamente
look have you seen have you seen the short that he
mira has visto has visto el short que
uploaded today on Twitter No well look jav
subió hoy a Twitter No pues mira jav
Javi Javi Javi Javi that I have three or
Javi Javi Javi Javi que tengo tres o
four companies I have I don't know how many
cuatro empresas tengo no sé cuántos
employees I have I don't know how many tasks
empleados tengo no sé cuántas tareas en
like I come here jaj Hehe but
plan que yo vengo aquí jaj Jeje pero que
I live in Narnia like I don't know I mean I haven't
yo vivo en Narnia en plan no sé O sea no
even seen the videos of the guys
me he visto ni los vídeos de los tíos a
that I have reported so you can get
los que he denunciado para que te hagas
an idea like I haven't had the time or
una idea en plan no he tenido tiempo ni
desire to see that, I've had to
ganas de ver eso ya lo he tenido que
delegate it to someone else. On Twitter, I see
delegar a otra persona yo en Twitter veo
what I can, I get drunk, I ignore half
lo que puedo me me casco de de la mitad
of the things, so obviously maybe the
de las cosas entonces obviamente quizá
same thing is happening to me as with kcu, with
me está pasando igual que con kcu con
kcu when we had the debate with dasas
kcu cuando hicimos el debate con dasas
nimu, I knew that cosc had done
nimu yo sabía que cosc lo había hecho
wrong but not that much, and when Dallas
mal pero no tanto y ya cuando me Dallas
gave me all the info, and all because
me pasó toda la info Y todo porque
Dallas is an encyclopedia, I mean, no, I, I would
Dallas es una enciclopedia o sea no yo
never want to have a problem
yo No querría tener nunca un problema
with d, he must tell you 20 things that
con d fue te debe sacar 20 cosas que no
you didn't even know existed, it's typical of
sabías ni tú que existen es lo típico de
a mother, no, where did I leave that, dasas
una madre no dónde he dejado eso dasas
knows where it is, so here it's
sabe dónde está entonces aquí sí que es
true that maybe if he did
cierto que quizás si él me hiciera toda
the whole compilation of everything for me, I'd say [ __ ].
la recopilación de todo diría [__]
Well, yeah, look, I'll give you that point. No, but
Pues sí Mira te doy ese punto No pero de
again, I don't have much
nuevo no tengo Tampoco yo eh mucho
interest either. And what you're saying, I think
interés Y eso que dices tú yo creo que
maybe I look the other way, but for something
quizá miro hacia otro lado pero por algo
very basic, and that's because for me, two
muy básico y es porque a mí que dos
people who get along with me
personas que se llevan bien conmigo se
fight each other. Honestly, if I can
pelean entre ellas Honestamente si puedo
mediate, I'm going to mediate.  I
mediar eh voy a mediar en su día lo
tried in fact I was the person who
intenté De hecho fui la persona que en
once suggested that they meet up so they
su día Les propuso que se vieran se
could talk
vieran juntos y que pudieran hablar
Dallas accepted Ricky that's when he said
Dallas aceptó Ricky fue cuando me dijo
no because of the restraining order
que no por lo de la orden de alejamiento
and that's why it wasn't carried out but
esta y por eso no se llevó a cabo pero
my idea has always been conciliatory with
mi idea siempre ha sido conciliadora con
them both but for example you recognize
ellos dos pero por ejemplo tú reconoces
that the restraining order is a
que lo de la orden de alejamiento es una
joke I don't understand the point there isn't an
payasada No entiendo el punto no hay una
order as such what I've told you
orden como tal lo que te lo he comentado
a thousand times is what he's told me
mil veces es lo que a mí me ha dicho yo
again I'm not a judge I'm not a lawyer this to him We
de nuevo no soy juez no soy abogado esto
'll have to ask Pablo
le Tendremos que preguntar a Pablo que
he'll know more but from what Ricky told me
él sabrá más pero por lo que me dijo
and I showed it to Dallas by
Ricky y se lo mostré a Dallas por por
text I sent him I think the photo
texto sea le mandé creo que la foto
we put up I put up an audio of him I put up an
pusimos lo puse un audio deblo puse un
audio of Pablo with the order eh exactly as it is there is
audio de Pablo con lo de la orden eh tal
n't I think an order as such what there
cual es no hay creo una orden como tal
is Is that he approaches there and
lo que hay Es que él se acerca ahí y
says hello this person is
dice hola esta persona me está
threatening me stop taking my life he
amenazando para de quitarme la vida me
's telling me this and he's telling me that
está diciendo esto y me está diciendo lo
and he's making these videos of me I
otro y me está haciendo estos vídeos
'm scared eh they say Okay well don't
tengo miedo eh dicen Vale pues no le
you answer if you answer him or meet up with him
respondas si le respondes o quedas con
or do anything you won't be able to
él o haces cualquier cosa no vas a poder
report it if something happens tomorrow and that's it there's
denunciar si mañana pasa algo y ya está
no
no hay
more that's what Ah And he translates that into
más es lo que Ah Y eso lo traduce él en
a restraining order Look by that
una orden de alejamiento Mira por esa
rule of three by that rule of three lerl
regla de tres por esa regla de tres lerl
had a restraining order from the
tenía una orden de alejamiento del
Postman because if he answered him
Cartero porque si le respondía le
the lawsuit would come to him joke joke joke
llegaba la demanda broma broma broma
joke eh
broma
Well eh what gossip do we have more
eh Bueno eh qué salseo tenemos más
pending apart from what happened with Ali what happened with
pendiente aparte de lo de al Ali lo de
Ali completely denied So
Ali completamente desmentido Entonces
what is this exclusive about gref that I have
qué es eso de exclusiva sobre gref que
n't seen this exclusive about
esto no lo he visto yo exclusiva sobre
gref and erti come on I'll tell it let's see
gref y erti venga va la cuento a ver
okay It turns out that in the next few
vale Resulta ser que en los próximos
days H I think the exact date is the 23rd
días H creo que la fecha exacta es el 23
okay mm heretics is going to release a video
vale mm heretics va a sacar un vídeo
parodying the hlan in which they are going to have
parodiando a los hlan en el que van a
fun categories and they are going to
tener categorías de cachondeo y se van a
make fun of people in the
cachondear de gente en la categoría
breakup of the year category yes but what are they going to do
ruptura del año sí pero qué van a hacer
like the rewind Oh lias and cora leaves him
como el rewind Ay lias y cora lo deja
with Jonathan no lias siora
con Jonathan no lias siora le pone los
cheats on Jonathan I mean are they going to do it
cuernos a Jonathan o sea van a hacerlo
right or are they going to do it  bad Oh I can't get there
bien o lo van a hacer mal Ay ya no llego
because Claro in the rewind they did a
porque Claro en el rewind hicieron una
well look at you in the rewind
bueno es que fíjate tú en el rewind
they were talking about a breakup and it's like let's see
hablaban de de ruptura y es como a ver
one thing is a breakup and another thing is the
una cosa son ruptura y otra cosa es lo
Ricky Lali thing
de Ricky Lali lo
about Jonata this Jonata no we'll see on
de jonata este jonata no ya lo veremos
the 23rd but people don't like
el día 23 peroa gente no le gusta el
gossip when it's against them eh the Bot
salseo cuando son contra ellos eh el Bot
the Bot took the message from Dallas But
el Bot le quitó el mensaje a Dallas Pero
I managed to read it eh I managed to
yo lo alcancé a leer eh lo alcancé a
read it
leer
Dallas man the [ __ ] starts taking down whatever
Dallas tío el [__] se pone a quitar lo
he wants and give if what you say is true then time will tell You know I'm a fair guy if he keeps lying to me because because he's allegedly lying to me then I'm going to end up realizing I mean there's no time time I'm serious but let's
tiempo al tiempo lo digo en serio pero a
see let's not call it bad weather
ver que no llamemos al mal tiempo
either but let's see it has been
tampoco pero a ver ha quedado ha quedado
settled and clarified I mean
ya zanjado y aclarado O sea a lo Llama a
what Ricky calls a restraining order
lo que Ricky llama orden de alejamiento
is that he went to the police station and
es a que ha ido a la comisaría y ha
said that a youtuber wants to hit him and he
dicho que un youtuber le quiere pegar y
probably handed over a screenshot of the
habrá entregado una captura de la
conversation and the policeman said
conversación y el policíal ha dicho
Okay, if he wants, wants You would be
Bueno pues si quiere quiere Te
interested in that when you get to
interesaría para cuando llegues al
trial that you are not responding to him, that
juicio que tú no estés respondiéndole
's what he calls a
eso es a lo que él llama orden de
restraining order okay, I mean no no no I mean it doesn't
alejamiento vale o sea no no no O sea
exist Damn There is no
que no existe [__] Que no hay orden de
restraining order basically
alejamiento básicamente
he's going to end up, he's going to end up coming up to get into trouble with me
queas va a terminaras va a terminar
How come
subiendo para meterme la bronca Cómo que
allegedly because for me it's not
presuntamente pues porque para mí no es
a lie that they tell me that they've
una mentira que me digan que te hayan
put a restraining order on you when
puesto una orden de alejamiento cuando
he interprets it that way It's
él lo interpreta de esa manera Es
simply an inaccuracy, when I
simplemente una in exactitud yo cuando
talk to my friends I'm not either You
hablo con mis amigos tampoco soy Tú lo
see it as a lie, let's see,
ves como una mentira eso a ver es que
because of that TR rule I put a
por esa regla de TR yo le una orden de
restraining order on H, even once on someone who
alejamiento H hasta una vez a uno que me
broke into my car and took the radio, damn,
abrió el coche y se llevó la radio cojon
let's see, you go to the police station and file
vamos ver tú vas a la comisaría y poner
the complaints then another thing is that,
las denuncias luego otra cosa es que el
let's see, a restraining order is when
vamos a ver una orden de alejamiento es
the judge sees an imminent danger in
que el juez vea un peligro inminente en
which he has to put a
que le tiene que poner una orden de
restraining order on a person and that
alejamiento a una persona y que esa
person cannot surround I don't know how many
persona no pueda rodear no sé cuántos
meters around you, he cannot be
metros alrededor de ti no pueda estar
around you because he is a danger
por alrededor tuya porque es un peligro
to you or  well Ricky doesn't go to the police station
para ti o sea Ricky no va a la comisaría
and
y
says I'll buy your point or I mean I'll
pone te compro el punto o sea te compro
totally buy your point but I think
el el el punto totalmente pero creo que
there's a context that is very easy to
hay un contexto que es muy fácil de
understand and that is that when I say to him
entender y es que cuando yo le digo e
look I have Dallas on that corner and you
mira tengo a Dallas en esa esquina y tú
and I are on this other one do you want to
y yo estamos en esta otra quieres que
meet with Dallas and record something or we
nos veamos con Dallas y grabamos algo O
talk or whatever and he says to me if you
hablamos o lo que sea y él me dice si
feel like it I'm not lacking but I can't because
ganas no me faltan pero no puedo porque
if tomorrow I want to report him I can't
si mañana lo quiero denunciar no puedo
because they told me that if I approach
porque me han dicho que si si me acerco
him I don't know I don't know how many I have a
a él no sé no sé cuántos tengo una orden
restraining order about the order Maybe it
de alejamiento lo de la orden A lo mejor
's a way of explaining it you know it's not
es una manera de explicarlo sabes no es
a lie an order to explain it
una mentira una orden de explicarlo
let's go yeah it's not again but you
vamos a sí no es de nuevo pero tú
understand that I don't know about those things
entiendes que yo no sé de que esas cosas
like if you tell me that it is 100% that's
en plan si tú me dices que eso es 100%
how Pablo told you I'll buy it and they've
así te lo ha dicho Pablo te lo compro y
lied to me but again since I don't
me han mentido pero de nuevo como yo no
know those issues the order is what it
sé esos temas la ordenamiento es lo que
is and I don't need Pablo to tell me
es y yo no necesito que me lo diga Pablo
like if I take it and a video of me
como si yo cojo y sale un vídeo mío
[ __ ] this doll comes out okay How did
follándome a este muñeco vale Cómo cómo
you escalate this so  quick poor Micky
has escalado esto tan rápido pobre Micky
and here I am giving the doll this
y me sale aquí yo dándole al muñeco esto
Pin Pin Pin Pin and you tell me Oh I
Pin Pin Pin Pin y tú me dices Ay te
was supporting Mickey Mao and I tell you
estab apoyando a Mickey Mao y yo te digo
no it's not a real doll of those
no no es una real doll de esas de las
that cost 15 bucks and look at you no You
que cuesta 15 pavos y mira tien no No te
're kneeling at Mickey you bastard he's
estas hincando al Mickey cabrón que está
all crazy period There's no way no
todo salido punto No hay hay manera no
no you can see it as an
no tú puedes verlo como una muñeca
inflatable doll but it's a Mickey Mouse from
hinchable pero es un Mickey Mouse de
Disneyland without more a
Disneylandia sin más una orden de
restraining order is that in the face of danger
alejamiento es que ante un peligro una
once the complaint is admitted for
vez que ya la denuncia es admitida a
processing and reaches the court the judge says there is
trámite y llega al juzgado el juz dice
a danger you understand I already understood the
hay un peligro entend Ya entendí el
point but I didn't want to cut you off before it
punto pero no te quise cortar antes me
seemed magical to me Mickey
parecía mágico lo de Mickey
Mouse one way to interpret it is that
Mouse una manera de interpretarlo es que
to you I'll buy you Look I'll buy you I'll
a ti te par te compro Mira te compro te
buy the point I mean I'm fair I'll
compro el punto o sea yo soy justo te
buy you the point that you have arguments
compro el punto que tenéis argumentos
Well yes he must have lied to me again no I don't
Pues sí me habrá mentido de nuevo no no
think it's a malicious lie that
creo que sea una mentira con maldad que
's where I'm going with this You know It
es donde yo le voy con la de esto Sabes
's touching me today I had thrown you out Here
Me está tocando hoy Te habí echado Aquí
let's see it's a lie it's not a one way one way
vamos a ver es una mentira no es una una
Look one way  of
forma una forma Mira una forma de
interpreting the things that you say that
interpretar las cosas que tú digas que
this Pink Mobile and me telling you that it is
este Movil Rosa y yo te diga que es
fuchsia those are ways of interpreting it
fucsia eso son formas de interpretarlo
but you saying that there is a
pero que tú digas que hay una orden de
restraining order when there isn't is not a
alejamiento cuando no la hay no es una
way of interpreting it because Ricky
manera de interpretarlo porque Ricky
knows very well that there is no
sabe de sobra que no hay ninguna orden
restraining order he knows very well that that cannot be
de alejamiento sabe de sobra que eso no
bought at Mercadona he is
se compra en el mercadona se lo está
making it up he is lying on purpose
inventando él está mintiendo a propósito
one thing is a mistake like
una cosa es una equivocación como lo
yours the other day with the turboplane
tuyo del otro día con lo de turboplane
is that you are wrong because you have no
es que te equivocas porque no tienes
knowledge but another thing is that he
conocimiento pero otra cosa es que él
having the knowledge invents
teniendo el conocimiento se invente una
something that does not exist he is lying on
cosa que no existe él está mintiendo a
purpose because he shits himself in a debate so
propósito porque se caga de un debate
that later they say that on this channel
para que luego digan que en este canal
we all Lemos our balls eh I am the
todos nos Lemos los huevos eh soy el
only one who receives [ __ ] they put me in from
único que recibe cabrones me meten por
all
todos
sides tomorrow I have four videos on the
lados mañana tengo cuatro vídeos en el
Dallas Channel I I used to be friends with
Canal de Dallas yo yo antes era amigo de
delox no but Ricky that I have
delox no pero que Ricky que yo no tengo
nothing I understand I understand your point I understand
nada Entiendo entiendo tu punto entiendo
your point of of everyone anyway
tu punto de de de todos de todos modos
eh I tell you for me the point is It is that
eh Te digo para mí el punto está Es que
for me it is very easy to give dala and the Bot
para mí es muy fácil dier dala y el Bot
does not ban  al delo for saying this [ __ ] he
no banea al delo por decir esta [__]
's a son of a [ __ ] dasas I would buy this from you
se es hijo de [__] dasas esto te lo
in a chupi Stream but here
compraría en un chupi Stream pero aquí
you're talking about chill No man no the the the
has hablando de chill No hombre no el el
point for me is that I understand
el el punto para mí es que yo entiendo
that he told me to make it quick and he
que él me lo dijo para hacerla rápida y
threw a triple at me maybe and and it could be eh
me tiró un triple quizá y y puede ser eh
that he [ __ ] himself like Dallas says it
que se cagara encima como dice Dallas
could be Dallas also I'm telling you it's
puede ser Dallas también te digo es que
because he's [ __ ] himself from a debate tod the
porque está cagado de un debate tod a
same thing happens to all of them they're very
todos les pasa lo mismo son muy
brave to make 50 videos about
valientes para hacerle 50 vídeos al
Dallas it happens to me too eh with
Dallas a mí también me pasa eh con
many eh They're very brave to tell me
muchos eh Son muy valiente para decirme
insult me Pin Pin but you challenge them to a
insultarme Pin Pin pero los retas un
debate and either they upload it and leave crying
debate y o bien suben y se van llorando
or they don't upload it and each one makes an
o bien no suben y cada uno pone una
excuse it's not that you want to monetize it's not
excusa no es que tú quieres monetizar no
that I don't know and Ricky's excuse is I've
es que no s y la escusa de Ricky es he
put a restraining order [ __ ] they've
puesto una orden de alejamiento [__] te
put a restraining order on you
han puesto a ti una orden de alejamiento
before tons of women who
antes que a montones de mujeres que
suffer you
sufren
must have seen the face of Poor thing my son is that
habrá visto cara de Pobrecita hijo mío
no no there is no
sea es que no no no hay orden de
restraining order but it's that there isn't even a
alejamiento pero es que ni siquiera hay
complaint this we're talking about that was already
denuncia esto estamos hablando que fue
How long  how long has this been going on Yes,
hace ya Cuánto cuánto hace esto ya Si
if that complaint had been
eso si esa denuncia hubiera sido
admitted for processing, they would have already
admitido a trámite ya se la hubieran
notified it, there would have been a trial no no yes yes yes there is
notificado ya hubiese habido juicio no
no order that
no que sí que sí que no hay orden que
we all agree on that, I have
eso estamos todos de acuerdo no teido
never had any doubts about it what I have
nunca dudas al respecto lo que te he
told you It is that for I mean there is no order the
dicho Es que para O sea no hay ord el
point that I understood that order to be is to
punto que yo entendía que esa orden es
say it is there is an order that if Dallas gets
decirlo es hay orden de que si Dallas se
close there is a sanction I understand that that
acerca hay una sanción entiendo que ese
is the problem I don't know what it says is I
es el problema no é lo que dice es No me
can't get close to Dallas in x Well then I ca
puedo acercar a Dallas en x Pues luego
n't report it without more I'm going to
no lo puedo denunciar sin más te voy a
tell you I buy the point but I find
decir te compro el punto pero me hace
Pedro's comment funny when he says
gracia el comentario de Pedro que dice
I want to be delox or micki to
Qué ganas de ser delox o micki para
receive No man no but not seeing me I don't care that I don't care
recibir No hombre no pero no ver a m me
what you
da igual que a mí me da igual lo que tú
think I'm telling you for your own good I mean in a
opines te lo digo por tu bien o sea en
way I'm going to tell you that I don't like
plan te voy a decir que que no me gusta
being a piata let's move on to another topic dude I've
ser piñata vamos a otro tema cabrón ya
already received
ya he recibido
enough no let's see he's left me
suficiente no a ver me ha dejado
kids kids
chavalería chavalería
send me kisses so I can recover my
mándenme besitos para que recupere los
spirits you just gave me a double chin
ánimos que me acaban de pegar una papada
in  live and I come here to say hello for free
en directo y yo de gratis vengo aquí a
and I go home drunk so you can knock out
saludar y me voy papeado a casa para que
But I'm telling you this so you don't sin
noqu Pero te lo digo para que no peques
innocent a Ricky has shat himself and that's it
inocente a se ha cagado el Ricky y ya
but you yes yes yes on top of that he is
está pero tú si si si es que encima es
resentful he eh has an ego that he
rencoroso es eh tiene un ego que no
shouldn't have because for example the other
debería tener pues por ejemplo el otro
day when you are dedicating yourself to
día cuando tú te estás dedicando al
gossip you with that ego you can't go
salseo tú con ese ego no puedes ir
because just as you are giving one day you
porque igual que tú estás dando un día
receive and you have to take it well take
recibes y te tienes que tomar bien [__]
and receive and that's it and if it's your turn it's your
y recibir y ya está y si te ha tocado te
turn and more when now he jokes about
ha tocado y más cuando ahora el bromea
the subject Look what a cuckold I am that
con el tema Mira qué cornudo soy que
I put a eh a very long tweet
pongo un eh un tweet larguísimo
parodying the enla now he doesn't care
parodiando los enla ahora no le importa
if they call him a cuckold but when
que le llamen cornudo pero cuando
we comment on the subject and we bring
nosotros comentamos el tema y traemos a
Tudor we did our job well done
tudor hicimos nuestro trabajo bien hecho
not like he does okay that he let's go it
no como él lo hace vale que que él vamos
's that many times he has asked me
es que él muchas veces me ha preguntado
about subjects and I have given him the information and
de temas y le he dado la información y
then he said it like the dick came out
luego lo ha dicho como la salido de la
because he was pissed off but he starts
[__] porque estaba picado pero se pone
saying It's not that it's normal that they remove
a decir No es que es normal que saquen a
the gossip channels from  the eslam
los canales de salseo de los eslam
because of course you imagine giving
porque claro es que tú imagínate darle
an award to someone who makes gossip it's like
un premio a uno que hace salseo es como
Look man, I mean Jorge Javier Vzquez
Mira tío o sea Jorge Javier Vázquez
has some [ __ ] waves what are you
tiene un [__] ondas qué me estás
telling me the TV factory has I don't
contando la fábrica de la tele tiene no
know how many awards also what are you
sé Cuántos premios también qué me estás
telling me man I mean you don't have a [ __ ]
diciendo tío O sea no tienes ni [__]
clue what you're talking about and you get on with it man I
idea de lo que habla y se pone hombre Yo
understand that you can call me a
entiendo que a mí me podéis Llamar canal
gossip channel but I do the gossip
de salseo pero yo el salseo lo hago
with respect not everyone can
desde el respeto eso todos no pueden
say the same thing I don't disrespect
decir lo mismo yo no le falto respeto a
anyone it's like Oh yes I've seen that
nadie es como Ah eso sí lo he visto eso
yes I've seen that dude well what I
sí lo he visto cabrón pues lo que te he
told you on Twitter I didn't think it was a
dicho en Twitter no pensaba que era un
tiktok related to the topic of daras
tiktok relacionado con el tema de daras
ilali sorry and he tells me with respect
ilali perdón y me dice desde el respeto
and like Sorry I mean we've seen you
y como Perdona O sea que te hemos visto
here 8000 times saying that little princess is
aquí 8000 veces decir que princesita es
a [ __ ] and that she sucks and that I don't know what I don't
una [__] y que la chupa y que no sé queé
know man of course eh I understand the
no sé hombre claro eh entiendo el el
point for me there yes I give it to you I think
punto para mí ahí sí te lo doy yo creo
you do a good job but not
que tú sí haces un buen trabajo pero no
only you I think there are more channels that
solo tú creo que hay más canales que
do  good job again I'm going to give
hacen un buen trabajo de nuevo voy a dar
those who I think do it I haven't seen
los que yo creo que lo hacen no he visto
all their videos please don't send me
todos sus vídeos por favor no me mandéis
to the stake again for not having seen
a la hoguera de nuevo por no haber visto
all the [ __ ] videos If at some
todos los [__] vídeos Si en algún
point they haven't seen it you have the worth tomorrow
momento no lo han la valia tienes mañana
I will please please He was never my
yo por favor por favor Nunca fue mi
friend he scammed me he scammed me I think they
amigo me estafó me estafó yo creo que lo
do it out of respect my feeling at
hacen desde el respeto mi sensación al
least the last videos that I've seen
menos los últimos vídeos que yo he visto
some cell phone no sisplau the news s
alguno cel no sisplau el noticieros s
cell and and the guy shur those two I see them
cel y y el tío shur esos dos yo los veo
very chills I see them quite a bit out of
muy chills los veo bastante desde el
respect
respeto
see I tell you my opinion I don't watch them much
ve te digo mi opinión no los veo mucho
because they don't get wet much Then since he gets
porque se mojan poco Entonces como se
a little wet I understand that they do it out of
moja un poco entiendo que lo hacen desde
respect eh No nauter yes I think that
el respeto eh No nauter sí creo que a
sometimes he sows quite a bit of discord nauter no I don't
veces mete bastante cizaña nauter no no
think he does it that much out of respect
creo que lo haga tanto desde el respeto
nauter yes I have seen him commit quite a few
nauter sí lo he visto cometer bastantes
infractions on more than one occasion but
infracciones en más de una ocasión pero
but still the nauter I must admit that
pero igual le nauter debo reconocer que
although I think that sometimes he swings Eh it makes me
aunque creo que a veces se columpia Eh
laugh
me hace me hace gracia a
sometimes I go to sleep say the bastard
veces me voy a dormir di el cabrón madre
my god I'm going to sleep  Go to sleep, dasas, go
mía voy a dormir vete a dormir dasas
to sleep, eh. By the way, dasas, eh,
vete a dormir eh Por cierto dasas eh
I'm free tomorrow, so we can play
mañana tengo libre en plan podemos echar
a game and talk before you
ahí una partidilla algo y hablamos antes
freeze me out four times, you son of a
de que me celes cuatro veces hijo de
[ __ ], a video is playing, damn, this
[__] está cascando un vídeo
is missing tomorrow, tomorrow we have
[__] está falta mañana mañana tenemos
tomorrow we have a debate, daras versus
mañana tenemos un debate daras versus
delox, the simo to success and allegedly there
delox el simo al éxito e presuntamente
was or wasn't a restraining order, eh,
hubo o no orden de alejamiento eh el
today's topic, well, I'll buy it, I'll buy it,
hoy bueno que te la compro que te la
don't
compro no te
worry [Music]
preocupes